Inventory of the Warner T. Jones 1819-1891
Earl Gregg Swem Library, College of William and Mary
Special Collections, Earl Gregg Swem Library, College of William and Mary
Warner T. Jones Papers 1891-1891.
Special Collections, Earl Gregg Swem Library, College of William and Mary
Mss. 39.1 J75
2,674 items.
Letters and business papers of Judge Warner T. Jones of Gloucester County, Virginia, 1807-1891.
John Randolph Bryan,; Joseph Bryan,; Samuel Bassett French,; J. B. H. (James Barron Hope),; Charles Triplett O'Ferrall,; John Randolph Tucker,; Lyon Gardiner Tyler,; Richard P. Jones,; Warner T. Jones,; John R. Page.
Administrative Information
Restrictions on Access
Collection is open to all researchers.
Acquisition Information
Purchased: 2,674 items, 4/28/1936.
Scope and Content Information
Papers, 1807-1891, of Warner T. Jones, judge of Gloucester County, Virginia; his brother Richard P. Jones; and his nephew John R. Page. Papers include letters concerning the Jones family and the Seawell family.
Prominent correspondents include John Randolph Bryan, Joseph Bryan, Samuel Bassett French, James Barron Hope, Charles Triplett O'Ferall, William Booth Taliaferro, John Randolph Tucker, and Lyon Gardiner Tyler. Collection includes printed advertisements for sewing and knitting machines
Arrangement
Organization
This collection is organized into three Series: 1. Correspondence, 2. Legal Papers, and 3. Miscellaneous Papers.
Arrangement
In the first series, the collection is arranged chronologically by date with those items without dates located at the end of each series. The first series is divided into subseries in ten year increments, resulting in six subseries. In the second series, the collection is arranged alphabetically by subject or persons last name. The seven subseries in the second series were created for subjects or persons with multiple folders.
Index Terms
Family Names:
Jones family.; Seawell family.
Persons:
Bryan, John Randolph, 1806- 1887.; Bryan, Joseph, 1845-1908.; French, Samuel Bassett, 1820-1898.; J. B. H. (James Barron Hope), 1829-1887.; O'Ferrall, Charles Triplett, 1840-1905.; Tucker, John Randolph, 1823-1897.; Tyler, Lyon Gardiner, 1853-1935.; Jones, Richard P.; Page, John R.
Subjects:
Sewing-- Equipment and supplies.; Sewing machines--History.; Knitting machines.; Warner Hall (Va.: Estate)
Geographical Names:
Gloucester County (Va.)--History--19th century.
Components List
  Series 1: Correspondence
- Correspondence, 1855-1891, n.d. (Box 1-2)
  This series is arranged in chronological order by date.
  - Letters, 1850-1859., 19 items. (Box-folder 1:1-19)
    - Lewis Hill, Richmond, [Virginia], to Warner T. Jones, n.p., 19 Feb. 1855., 1 page. ALS. (Box-folder 1:1)
    - Lewis Hill, Richmond, [Virginia], to Warner T. Jones, n.p., 27 March 1855., 1 page. ALS. (Box-folder 1:2)
    - Lewis Hill, Richmond, [Virginia], to Warner T. Jones, n.p., 4 April 1855., 1 page. ALS. (Box-folder 1:3)
    - Christian & Barry, Columbus, Miss[issippi], to Warner T. Jones, Gloucester Co[urt] Ho[use], Vir[ginia], 28 Nov. [18]55., 1 page. ALS. (Box-folder 1:4)
    - W[illia]m Taliaferro, Church Hill, [Virginia], to Warner [T. Jones], n.p., 3 Dec. 1855., 1 page. ALS. (Box-folder 1:5)
    - Tho[ma]s C. Robins, Gloucester, Virginia, to Warner T. Jones, Richmond, Virginia, 15 Dec. 1855., 1 page. ALS. (Box-folder 1:6)
    - C. C. Curtis, n.p., to Warner T. Jones, 14 Jan. 1856., 1 page. ALS. (Box-folder 1:7)
    - P. A. Peterson, Gloucester, Virginia, to Warner T. Jones, n.p., 18 Feb. [18]56., 2 page2. ALS. (Box-folder 1:8)
    - Lewis Hill, Richmond, [Virginia], to Warner T. Jones, Glouc[ester, Virginia], 16 July 1856., 1 page. ALS. (Box-folder 1:9)
      Enclosure: Certificate of deposit on Bank of Virginia, Richmond, [Virginia].
    - Lewis Hill, Richmond, [Virginia], to Warner T. Jones, n.p., 12 Aug. 1856., 1 page. ALS. (Box-folder 1:10)
    - Lewis Hill, Richmond, [Virginia], to Warner T. Jones, n.p., 30 Oct. 1856., 1 page. ALS. (Box-folder 1:11)
    - Sprague & Rook, Baltimore, [Md.], to Warner T. Jones, Gloucester C[ourt] H[ouse], Virginia, 26 Nov. [18]56., 1 page. ALS. (Box-folder 1:12)
    - Jo[h]n A. B. Thornton, Gloucester, [Virginia], to Warner T. Jones, Richmond, Virginia, 15 Dec. 1857., 2 pages. ALS. (Box-folder 1:13)
    - Jeremiah Hall, Circleville, Pickaway County, Ohio, to Warner T. Jones, n.p., 14 Jan. 1858., 1 page. ALS. (Box-folder 1:14)
      Enclosure: Business card of Jeremiah Hall, attorney-at-law.
    - Richard P. Jones, Lands End, Gloucester [County, Virginia], to his brother, Warner T. Jones, Richmond, Virginia, 15 Jan. 1858., 4 page. ALS. (Box-folder 1:15)
    - Wyndham Kemp, Clifford, [Virginia], to Warner T. Jones, Richmond, Virginia, 25 Jan. 1858., 2 pages. ALS. (Box-folder 1:16)
    - Benja[min] Polland, Richmond, [Virginia], to Wyndham Kemp, Gloucester Courthouse, [Virginia], 21 May 1858., 1 page. ALS. (Box-folder 1:17)
    - J. Holt, Commissioner, United States Patent Office, Washington, D.C., to John R. Page, Sec[retary], Gloucester Co[unty] Ag[ricultural] soc[iety], Gloucester C[ourt] H[ouse], Virginia, 26 Nov. 1858., 2 pages. APD. (Box-folder 1:18)
      Enclosure: Printed questionnaire concerning agricultural associations. 1 Nov. 1858. 3 pages. PD.
    - Ro[bert] H. Armistead, W[illia]msburg, [Virginia], to Warner T. Jones, Richmond, Virginia, 28 Dec. 1859., 1 page. ALS. (Box-folder 1:19)
  - Letters, 1860-1869., 37 items. (Box-folder 1:20-57)
    - F. L. Taylor, Belle Farm, Gloucester C[ourt] H[ouse], Virginia, to Warner T. Jones, Richmond, Virginia, 11 Jan. 1860., 4 pages. ALS. (Box-folder 1:20)
    - J. C. Sheldon, Wilson's Creek, [Gloucester County, Virginia], to Col. [Warner T. Jones], n.p., 27 Feb. 1860., 1 page. ALS. (Box-folder 1:21)
    - Ja[me]s M. Goggin, Memphis, Tennessee, to Doctor [?], n.p., 3 March [18]60., 6 pages. ALS. (Box-folder 1:22)
    - Ja[me]s M. Goggin, Memphis, Tennessee, to Doctor [?], n.p., 14 May [18]60., 5 pages. ALS. (Box-folder 1:23)
    - Boliva Christian, Staunton, [Virginia], to W[arner] T. Jones, n.p., 26 July 1860., 3 pages. ALS. (Box-folder 1:24)
    - C. M. Conrad, New Orleans, La., to Warner [T.] Jones, Richmond, Virginia, 4 Jan. 1861., 1 page. ALS. (Box-folder 1:25)
    - Jo[h]n Hibble, Cappahosic, Gloucester Co[unty], Virginia, to Warner T. Jones, 9 Jan. 1861., 2 page. ALS. (Box-folder 1:26)
    - Robert R. Berry, Gloucester County, Virginia, to W[arner] T. Jones, Richmond, Virginia, 7 Feb. 1861., 1 page. ALS. (Box-folder 1:27)
    - [?], Burleigh, [?], to "My dear Cousin," n.p., 8 Feb. 1861., 2 page. AL. Incomplete. (Box-folder 1:28)
    - Jesse Thomas, Gloucester C[oun]ty, Virginia, to Warner T. Jones, n.p., 14 March 1861., 1 page. ALS. (Box-folder 1:29)
    - 1 page. ALS. (Box-folder 1:30)
    - A. F. Hopkins, Mobile, [Alabama], to Warner T. Jones, Gloucester C[ourt] House, Virginia, 4 May 1861., 4 pages. ALS. (Box-folder 1:31)
    - Jo[h]n L. Hibble, Cappahosic, Gloucester Co[unty], Virginia, to Warner T. Jones, Gloucester Co[urt] Ho[use], Virginia, 6 July 1861., 2 pages. ALS. (Box-folder 1:32)
    - Jeff[erson] W. Stubbs, Valley Front, Gloucester Co[unty, Virginia], to Warner T. Jones, Gloucester C[our]t House, Virginia, 27 Aug. 1861., 1 page. ALS. (Box-folder 1:33)
    - [?], Richmond, [Virginia], to "Dear Brother," n.p., 6 June 1862., 6 pages. AL. Incomplete. (Box-folder 1:34)
    - Jo[h]n W. C. Catlett, Timberneck, [Gloucester County; Virginia], to Warner [T. Jones], n.p., 30 Sept. 1862., 1 page. ALS. (Box-folder 1:35)
    - I. B. Ash, at the camp of the 34th V[irgini]a Reg[imen]t, near Petersburg, Virginia, to his brother, George D. Ash, Gloucester County, Virginia, 13 March 1865., 4 pages. ALS. (Box-folder 1:36)
    - John [?], Co. E, 26th Virginia Inf[an]t[ry], to Miss D. A. Minor, Gloucester County, [Virginia], 18 March 1865., 4 page. ALS. (Box-folder 1:37)
    - Jo[h]n Campbell, Weldon, N.C., to Warner T. Jones, n.p., 24 March 1865., 1 page. ALS. (Box-folder 1:38)
    - Willie S[eawell], Fluvanna Co[unty], Virginia, to Laura Johnston, Gloucester Co[unty], Virginia, 6 April 1865., 1 page. ALS. (Box-folder 1:39)
    - Will S[eawell], Fluvanna [County], Virginia, to his father, W[illia]m H. Seawell, Gloucester County, Virginia, 6 April 1865., 1 page. ALS. (Box-folder 1:40)
    - E. H. Rowe, n.p., to Warner T. Jones, n.p., 2 May 1865., 1page. ALS. (Box-folder 1:41)
    - Alex G. McChesney, M.D., Hot Springs, [Bath County, Virginia], to [?], n.p., 26 Aug. 1865., 1 page. ALS. (Box-folder 1:42)
    - B. R. Wellford, Jr., Richmond, [Virginia], to Warner T. Jones, n.p., 23 Feb. 1866., 1 page. ALS. (Box-folder 1:43)
    - J. C. Sheldon, Allen's Grove, [Virginia ?], to Col. [Warner T. Jones], n.p., 16 April 1866., 4 pages. ALS. (Box-folder 1:44)
    - J[oh]n Page, Longwood, [Virginia ?], to Warner [T. Jones], n.p., 15 Jan. 1867., 2 page. ALS. (Box-folder 1:45)
    - B. R. Wellford, Jr., Richmond, [Virginia], to Warner T. Jones, n.p., 1 June 1867., 1 page. ALS. (Box-folder 1:46)
    - Warner T. Jones, Lands End, Gloucester Co[unty, Virginia], to Jo[h]n R. Page, Carysbrook, [Fluvanna County, Virginia], 19 July 1867., 4 pages. ALS. (Box-folder 1:47)
    - Jo[h]n R. Page, Alexandria, Virginia, to W[arner] T. Jones, n.p., 22 Aug. 1867., 4 pages. ALS. (Box-folder 1:48)
    - John K. Forrer, Mossy Creek, Augusta Co[unty], Virginia, to W[illia]m Dobbins, n.p., 22 Nov. [18]67., 2 pages. ALS. (Box-folder 1:49)
    - J. R. Bryan, Carysbrook, [Fluvanna County, Virginia], to Warner T. Jones, Hickory Fork P[ost] O[ffice], Gloucester County, Virginia, 14 March 1868., 2 page. ALS. (Box-folder 1:50)
    - J. A. Cowardin & H. K. Ellyson, Richmond, [Virginia], to W[arner] T. Jones, n.p., 25 May 1868., 1 page. ALS. (Box-folder 1:51)
    - Tho[ma]s B. Rowe, Camden, Glo[ucester] Co[unty], Virginia, to Thomas E. Johnson, n.p., 2 Sept. 1868., 1 page. ALS. (Box-folder 1:52)
    - E. H. Rowe, n.p., to Warner T. Jones, n.p., 17 Feb. 1869., 1 page. ALS. (Box-folder 1:53)
    - Warner T. Jones, Lands End, Gloucester Co[unty, Virginia], to J. R. Bryan, Carysbrook, [Fluvanna County, Virginia], 23 March [18]69., 4 pages. ALS. (Box-folder 1:54)
    - J. R. Bryan, Carysbrook, [Fluvanna County, Virginia], to W[arner] T. Jones, n.p., 15 April 1869., 1 page. ALS. (Box-folder 1:55)
    - J. R. Bryan, Carysbrook, [Fluvanna County, Virginia], to W[arner] T. Jones, n.p., 7 June 1869., 2 pages. ALS. (Box-folder 1:56)
    - J. R. Bryan, Carysbrook, [Fluvanna County, Virginia], to W[arner] T. Jones, n.p., 1 Nov. [18]69., 3 pages. ALS. (Box-folder 1:57)
  - Letters, 1870-1879., 75 items. (Box-folder 1-2:58-134)
    - J. R. Bryan, Carysbrook, [Fluvanna County, Virginia], to Warner T. Jones, n.p., 3 May [18]70., 1 page. ALS. (Box-folder 1:58)
    - J. R. Bryan, Carysbrook, [Fluvanna County, Virginia], to [Warner T. Jones], n.p., 14 May [18]70., 2 pages. ALS. (Box-folder 1:59)
      Enclosure: Memorandum of an address.
    - J. R. Bryan, Carysbrook [Fluvanna County, Virginia], to [Warner T. Jones], n.p., 12 July 1870., 3 pages. ALS. (Box-folder 1:60)
    - Tazewell Taylor, n.p., to Warner T. Jones, Gloucester C[ourt] H[ouse], Virginia, 16 Nov. 1870., 1 page. ALS. (Box-folder 1:61)
    - St. G[eo]r[ge] Bryan, Greenway, [Virginia], to W[arner] T. Jones, n.p., 17 Dec. 1870., 2 page.s ALS. (Box-folder 1:62)
    - Maxwell T. Clarke, Richmond, Virginia, to Warner T. Jones, Gloucester Co[urt] Ho[use], Virginia, 27 Feb. [18]71., 1 page. ALS. (Box-folder 1:63)
    - A. S. Buford, Richmond, Virginia, to Warner T. Jones, Gloucester Co[urt] House, Virginia, 13 March 1871., 1 page. ALS. (Box-folder 1:64)
    - J. R. Bryan, Carysbrook, [Fluvanna County, Virginia], to W[arner] T. Jones, n.p., 4 May [18]71., 2 pages. ALS. (Box-folder 1:65)
    - J. R. Bryan, Carysbrook, [Fluvanna County, Virginia], to W[arner] T. Jones, n.p., 20 June 1871., 2 pages. ALS. (Box-folder 1:66)
    - R. D. Lee, Warwick Co[unty, Virginia], to Warner T. Jones, York Town Post Office, [Virginia], 4 Sept. 1871., 1 page. ALS. (Box-folder 1:67)
    - Th[oma]s B. Rowe, Woodstock, Middlesex Co[unty], Virginia, to W[arner] T. Jones, n.p., 5 Oct. 1871., 3 pages. ALS. (Box-folder 1:68)
    - J. R. Bryan, Columbia P[ost] O[ffice], [Fluvanna County, Virginia], to W[arner] T. Jones, n.p., 6 Oct. [18]71., 2 pages. ALS. (Box-folder 1:69)
    - J. R. Ross, Dragon Ordinary, Virginia, to Warner T. Jones, n.p., 10 Oct. 1871., 1 page. ALS. (Box-folder 1:70)
    - J. H. Henry, Richmond, Virginia, to Warner T. Jones, Gloucester C[our]t Ho[use], Virginia, 15 Nov. 1871., 1 page. ALS. (Box-folder 1:71)
    - C.C. Curtis, Richmond, Virginia, to his uncle, [Warner T. Jones], n.p., 29 Nov. 1871., 1 page. ALS. (Box-folder 1:72)
    - W[illia]m H. Shield, Jr., Yorktown, [Virginia], to Warner T. Jones, n.p., 1 Dec. [18]71., 3 pages. ALS. (Box-folder 1:73)
    - Wyndham Kemp, Clifford, [Virginia], to Warner T. Jones, Richmond, Virginia, 5 Jan. 1872., 2 pages. ALS. (Box-folder 1:74)
    - Edw[ard] C. Darlington, Yorktown, Virginia, to W[arner] T. Jones, n.p., 19 Jan. [18]72., 3 pages. ALS. (Box-folder 1:75)
    - J. C. Baytop, Gloucester C[ourt] H[ouse, Virginia], to Warner T. Jones, Richmond, Virginia, 20 Jan. [18]72., 1 page. ALS. (Box-folder 1:76)
    - M. B. Seawell, Gloucester C[ourt] H[ouse, Virginia], to Warner T. Jones, Richmond, [Virginia], 24 Jan. 1872., 1 page. ALS. (Box-folder 1:77)
    - Tho[ma]s E. Ballard, Richmond, Virginia, to W[arner] T. Jones, n.p., 31 Jan. 1872., 1 page. ALS. (Box-folder 1:78)
    - M. B. Seawell, Mathews C[ourt] H[ouse, Virginia], to Warner T. Jones, Richmond, [Virginia], 13 Feb. 1872., 3 pages. ALS. (Box-folder 1:79)
    - C. E. Minor, Hickory Fork P[ost] O[ffice], Gloucester Co[unty], Virginia, to Warner T. Jones, Richmond, Virginia, 15 Feb. 1872., 1 page. ALS. (Box-folder 1:80)
    - Jo[h]n S. Cooke, Glo[ucester] C[ourt] H[ouse, Virginia], to W[arner] T. Jones, n.p. 17 Feb. 1872., 1 page. ALS. (Box-folder 1:81)
    - W. R. Willis, Hampton, Virginia, to Warner T. Jones, Richmond, Virginia, 20 Feb. 1872., 2 pages. ALS. (Box-folder 1:82)
    - J. Prosser Tabb, Ditchley, [Virginia], to Warner T. Jones, n.p., 28 Feb. 1872., 4 pages. ALS. (Box-folder 1:83)
    - John W. Johnston, Washington, [D.C.], Warner T. Jones, Richmond, Virginia, 29 Feb. 1872., 3 pages. ALS. (Box-folder 1:84)
    - T. C. Baytop, Cappahosic, Gloucester C[oun]ty, [Virginia], to Col. Warner T. Jones & Major Perrin, n.p., 14 March [18]72., 1 page. ALS. (Box-folder 1:85)
      Enclosure: Summons in the suit Jo[h]n P. Sutton vs. W[illia]m Haynes, Gloucester County, [Virginia]. Signed by Thomas R. [Rile ?], J. P. 9 March 1872.
    - Warner T. Jones, Richmond, Virginia, to John T. Seawell, Gloucester Co[unty], Virginia, 18 March 1872., 1 page. ALS. (Box-folder 1:86)
    - Jo[h]n R. Page, Baltimore, Md., to Warner T. Jones, Richmond, Virginia, 25 March 1872., 1 page. ALS. (Box-folder 1:87)
    - W. R. Willis, Hampton, Virginia, to Warner T. Jones, Richmond, Virginia, 3 Ap[ril] 1872., 1 page. ALS. (Box-folder 1:88)
    - Sue H. Shield, Gloucester Co[unty, Virginia] to [Warner T.] Jones, n.p., 4 Jan. 1873., 1 page. ALS. (Box-folder 1:89)
    - J. C. Baytop, Gloucester Co[urt] Ho[use], Virginia, to W[arner] T. Jones, n.p., 7 Jan. 1873., 3 pages. ALS. (Box-folder 1:90)
    - Warner T. Jones, Richmond, Virginia to Sue [H. Shield], n.p., 10 Jan. 1872 i.e. 1873., 1 page. ALS. (Box-folder 1:91)
    - J. N. Stubbs, Gloucester Co[urt] Ho[use], Virginia, to Col. [Warner T. Jones], n.p., 10 Jan 1873., 3 pages. ALS. (Box-folder 1:92)
    - John T. Seawell, Gloucester Co[urt] Ho[use, Virginia], to W[arner] T. Jones, n.p., 26 Jan. 1873., 2 pages. ALS. (Box-folder 1:93)
    - Jeff[erson] W. Stubbs, Cappahosic, Gloucester County, [Virginia], to Warner T. Jones, n.p., 5 Feb. 1873., 2 pages. ALS. (Box-folder 1:94)
    - R. M. Booker, Hampton, Virginia, to [Warner T. Jones], n.p., 11 Feb. 1873., 3 pages. ALS. (Box-folder 1:95)
    - Jeff[erson] W. Stubbs, Cappahosic, Gloucester County, [Virginia], to Warner T. Jones, n.p., 18 Feb. 1873., 2 pages. ALS. (Box-folder 1:96)
    - John S. Cooke, Gloucester C[ourt] H[ouse], Virginia, to Warner T. Jones, Richmond, Virginia, 25 Feb. 1873., 3 pages. ALS. (Box-folder 1:97)
    - [Gilbert C.] Walker, [Governor of Virginia], 11 March 1873., 1 page. ALS. (Box-folder 1:98)
      Invitation to a reception.
    - W[illia]m B. Taliaferro, Gloucester C[our]t Ho[use, Virginia], to W[arner] T. Jones, n.p., 12 March 1873., 2 pages. ALS. (Box-folder 1:99)
    - W[illia]m F. Taylor, Richmond, Virginia, to Warner T. Jones, Gloucester C[ourt] H[ouse], Virginia, 14 April 1873., 1 page. ALS. (Box-folder 1:100)
    - Walker F. Jones, n.p., to Warner T. Jones, Glo[ucester] Co[urt] Ho[use, Virginia], 29 June 1873., 3 pages. ALS. (Box-folder 1:101)
    - W[illia]m H. Richardson, Lexington, Virginia, to Warner T. Jones, Gloucester Court House, Virginia, 5 July 1873., 1 page. ALS. (Box-folder 1:102)
    - J. Bell Bigger, Richmond, Virginia, to Warner T. Jones, n.p., 23 Aug. 1873., 1 page. ALS. (Box-folder 1:103)
    - J. L. Kemper, Gordonsville, [Orange County, Virginia], to Warner T. Jones, Gloucester C[ourt] H[ouse], Virginia, 30 Aug. 1873., 1 page. ALS. (Box-folder 1:104)
    - James Barron Hope, Norfolk, Virginia, to Warner T. Jones, Gloucester C[ourt] H[ouse], Virginia, 5 Dec. 1873., 1 page. ALS. (Box-folder 1:105)
    - Joseph L. Young, Norfolk, Virginia, to Warner T. Jones, Gloucester Co[urt] Ho[use], Virginia, 21 Jan. 1874., 1 page. ALS. (Box-folder 1:106)
      Including a note by Ja[me]s Barron Hope, Norfolk, Virginia, to Warner T. Jones, Gloucester Co[urt] Ho[use], Virginia
      Enclosure: Account due The Norfolk Landmark by Warner T. Jones. 1 p. AD. 13 July 1874.
    - B. F. Bland, John W. Lawson and C. B. Duffield, Richmond, Virginia, to Judge Warner T. Jones, Gloucester C[ourt] H[ouse], Gloucester Co[unty], Virginia, 22 April 1874., 1 page. ALS. (Box-folder 1:107)
      Official notification of Warner T. Jones' election as judge for Gloucester County.
    - R. T. Daniel, Richmond, Virginia, to Warner T. Jones, Gloucester C[ourt] H[ouse], Virginia, 3 Aug. 1874., 1 page. ALS. (Box-folder 1:108)
    - J. F. Hubbard, Yorktown, Virginia, to Warner T. Jones, Gloucester Court house, Gloucester County, Virginia, 22 Oct. 1874., 1 page. ALS. (Box-folder 1:109)
    - Warner T. Jones, Gloucester Co[urt] Ho[use], Virginia, to J. F. Hubbard, Yorktown, Virginia, 27 Oct. 1874., 1 page. ALS. (Box-folder 1:110)
    - A. Y. Stokes & Co., Richmond, Virginia, to Warner T. Jones, Gloucester Co[urt] Ho[use], Virginia, 9 Nov. 1874., 1 page. ALS. (Box-folder 1:111)
    - Cha[rle]s C. Curtis, Richmond, Virginia, to W[arner] T. Jones, Gloucester C[ourt] H[ouse], Virginia, 27 Nov. 1874., 2 pages. ALS. (Box-folder 1:112)
    - W[illia]m B. Taliaferro, Richmond, Virginia, to Warner T. Jones, Gloucester C[our]t Ho[use], Virginia, 12 Dec. 1874., 2 pages. ALS. (Box-folder 1:113)
    - J. N. Stubbs, Valley Front, [Gloucester County, Virginia], to Warner T. Jones, Glo[ucester] C[ourt] H[ouse], Virginia, 16 Feb. 1875., 1 page. ALS. (Box-folder 1:114)
    - Stokes & Lathrop for Stokes & Walker, Richmond, Virginia, to Judge Warner T. Jones, Gloucester Co[urt] Ho[use], [Virginia], 4 Mar. 1875., 2 pages. LS. (Box-folder 1:115)
    - Charles L. Pearson, Trenton, N. J., to B.B. Douglas, n.p., 7 April 1875., 2 pages. ALS. (Box-folder 1:116)
      Including a note by B.B. Douglas, n.p., to W[arner] T. Jones, n.p. dated 18 April 1875.
    - John L. Perrin, Ditchley, [Vat], to W[arner] T. Jones, Gloucester C[our]t Ho[use], Virginia, 14 June 1875., 1 page. ALS. (Box-folder 1:117)
    - Jo[h]n R. Page, University of Virginia, Charlottesville, Virginia, Warner T. Jones, Gloucester C[ourt] H[ouse], Virginia, 1 Aug. 1875., 2 pages. ALS. (Box-folder 1:118)
    - John N. Martin, Belle Farm, [Gloucester County, Virginia], to Warner [T.] Jones, Gloucester County, Virginia, 4 Sept. 1875., 2 pages. ALS. (Box-folder 1:119)
    - S. H. Boykin, Secretary, [Virginia] State Board of Immigration, Richmond, Virginia, to Warner T. Jones, Gloucester County, [Virginia], 30 Sept. 1875., 1 page. Printed circular letter. (Box-folder 1:120)
    - S. Bassett French, Secretary, Board of Managers, Lee Monument Association, Richmond, Virginia, to Judge [Warner T. Jones], Gloucester Court Ho[use], Virginia, 20 Nov. 1875., 1 page. Printed circular letter signed. (Box-folder 1:121)
    - P. M. T[hompson], Williamsburg, Virginia, to Warner T. Jones, n.p., 31 Dec. 1875., 3 pages. ALS. (Box-folder 1:122)
      Re: financial conditions at the College of William & Mary.
    - W[illia]m B. Taliaferro, Richmond, Virginia, to W[arner] T. Jones, n.p., 16 Jan. 1876., 4 pages. ALS. (Box-folder 2:123)
    - T. L. P. Cocke, Derwent, post marked Cartersville, [Cumberland County, Virginia], to W[arner] T. Jones, Gloucester C[ourt] H[ouse], Virginia, 15 March 1876., 3 pages. ALS. (Box-folder 2:124)
    - Letitia Tyler Semple, Richmond, [Virginia], to Warner T. Jones, Gloucester C[ourt] House, Virginia, 28 Oct. 1876., 6 pages. ALS. (Box-folder 2:125)
    - I. M. Parr & Son, Baltimore, Md., to W[arner] T. Jones, Gloucester C[ourt] H[ouse], Virginia, 8 Aug. 1878., 1 page. ALS. (Box-folder 2:126)
    - C.C. Curtis, Richmond, [Virginia], to "Uncle" [Warner T. Jones], n.p., 21 Oct. 1878., 1 page. ALS. (Box-folder 2:127)
    - Arch[ibal]d Taylor, Richmond, Virginia, to Warner T. Jones, Gloucester C[ourt] H[ouse], Virginia, 8 March 1879., 3 pages. ALS. (Box-folder 2:128)
    - James E. Byrd, Baltimore, [Md.], to Warner T. Jones, Gloucester County, Virginia, 21 April 1879., 1 page. ALS. (Box-folder 2:130)
    - P. N. Page, Goshen, [Gloucester County, Virginia], to "Uncle" [Warner T. Jones], n.p., 14 Aug. [18]79., 2 pages. ALS. (Box-folder 2:131)
    - F. E. J[?], Enfield, [Virginia], to Warner T. Jones, Gloucester C[ourt] H[ouse, Virginia], 24 Oct. [18]79., 1 page. ALS. (Box-folder 2:132)
    - A. L. U. Rogers, Richmond, [Virginia], to W[arner] T. Jones, n.p., 20 Nov. 1879., 2 pages. ALS. (Box-folder 2:133)
    - W[illia]m B. Taliaferro, Richmond, [Virginia], to W[arner] T. Jones, n.p., 8 Dec. 1879., 4 pages. ALS. (Box-folder 2:134)
  - Letters, 1880-1889., 83 items. (Box-folder 2:135-220)
    - Ja[me]s R. Ellerson, Richmond, Virginia, to Warner T. Jones, Gloucester C[ourt] H[ouse], Virginia, 2 Jan. 1880., 1 page. ALS. (Box-folder 2:135)
    - John W. Cringan, Richmond, Virginia, to W[arner] T. Jones, Gloucester C[ourt] H[ouse], Virginia, 15 Jan. 1880., 2 pages. ALS. (Box-folder 2:136)
    - E. M. Crump, New Kent C[our]t Ho[use], Virginia, to J. S. Cooke, Gloucester C[ourt] H[ouse], Virginia, 25 Feb. [18]80., 1 page. ALS. Postal card. (Box-folder 2:137)
    - P. N. Page, Gloucester C[ourt] H[ouse, Virginia], to "Uncle" Warner T. Jones, n.p., 27 Feb. 1880., 2 page. ALS. (Box-folder 2:138)
    - B. R. W[ellford], Jr., Richmond, Virginia, to Warner T. Jones, Gloucester Co[urt] Ho[use], Virginia, 31 Mar. [18]80., 1 page. ALS. Postal card. (Box-folder 2:139)
    - B. R. Wellford, Jr., Richmond, Virginia, to Warner T. Jones, Gloucester Co[urt] Ho[use], Virginia, 19 Apr[il] [18]80., 4 pages. ALS. (Box-folder 2:140)
    - L. R. Warren, Special Agent, Virginia Fire and Marine Insurance Co., Richmond, Virginia, to Warner T. Jones, Gloucester C[ourt] H[ouse], Virginia, 17 Aug. 1880., 1 page. ALS. (Box-folder 2:141)
    - D'Arcy P. Taliaferro, Norfolk, Virginia, to Warner T. Jones, Gloucester C[ourt] H[ouse, Virginia], 7 June 1881., 2 pages. ALS. (Box-folder 2:142)
    - R. A. Brock, Corresponding Secretary and Librarian, Virginia Historical Society, Richmond, Virginia, to Warner Throgmorton [sic] Jones, Gloucester C[ourt] H[ouse], Virginia, 20 July 1881., 1 page. Printed circular letter. (Box-folder 2:143)
    - Kirkpatrick & Blackford, Lynchburg, Virginia, to Warner T. Jones, Gloucester C[ourt] H[ouse], Virginia, 22 Nov. 1883., 1 page. ALS. (Box-folder 2:144)